(Sheldon:)Which only sits on alternate years.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and by the way,
it sits over there.
(Penny:)Come on, that is ridiculous.
(Leonard:)She's right. A committee that
important should meet more often.
(Penny:)That's not what I'm saying.
(Leonard:)This is the thing
about me standing up to him
(Leonard:)and not letting him run my life?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Raj:)That.
(Sheldon:)Okay. I think we've
found the problem here.
(Sheldon:)It's not the table at all.
(Penny:)It's you.
(Penny:)Me?
(Leonard:)It's always me,
take one for the team.
(Sheldon:)I have spent years
turning this lump of clay
(Sheldon:)into an acceptable conduit
for my will,
(Sheldon:)and then you came along
and reshaped him,
(Sheldon:)with your newfangled ideas
and your fancy genitals.
(Penny:)Are you gonna let him
talk to me like this?
"Fancy" sounds like a compliment.
(Penny:)Okay, I have not tried
to change Leonard.
(Penny:)That's just what happens
in relationships.
(Penny:)Look how much Amy's changed you.
(Sheldon:)-That's not true.
-Please.
(Penny:)When I first met you,
you were incapable
(Penny:)of touching another human being.
(Penny:)Now you're holding hands,
you're going on dates,